bikebandit.com 2019-07-23

# BikeBandit.com Help and Customer Service

Help > Privacy & Security

Why is Shopping at BikeBandit.com Secure?

When you shop at BikeBandit.com, you'll be one of thousands of our customers who safely shop with us every month. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure online commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

**The BikeBandit.com Secure Shopping Guarantee** protects you while you shop at BikeBandit.com so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. We guarantee that every transaction you make at BikeBandit.com will be safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card at BikeBandit.com. Under the [Fair Credit Billing Act,](http://www.ftc.gov/enforcement/rules/rulemaking-regulatory-reform-proceedings/fair-credit-billing-act) your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50, BikeBandit.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50. BikeBandit.com will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at BikeBandit.com while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

While BikeBandit.com uses encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, BikeBandit.com also protects your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which BikeBandit.com stores personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Back to top

How Does BikeBandit.com Protect Your Privacy?

BikeBandit.com protects your privacy in five different ways:

  1. We encrypt all credit card information.
  2. We don't store credit card information online.
  3. We never share, sell or disclose any customer information - including your email address - to anyone. Ever. Period.
  4. We follow the BBB guidelines for online security and customer privacy.
  5. We respect our customer wishes to be removed from our mailing list.

BikeBandit.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. BikeBandit.com only has access to and collects information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. BikeBandit.com will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.

You can do the following at any time by contacting us:

  * See what data BikeBandit.com has about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data BikeBandit.com has about you.
  * Have us delete any data BikeBandit.com has about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

Back to top

BikeBandit.com Privacy Notice

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for BikeBandit.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by the BikeBandit.com web site. It will notify you of the following: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the BikeBandit.com web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. We follow the BBB guidelines for online security and customer privacy.
  5. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

BikeBandit.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. BikeBandit.com only has access to and collects information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. BikeBandit.com does not sell or rent this information to anyone.

BikeBandit.com will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. BikeBandit.com will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

We use technologies, such as cookies, to customize content and advertising, to provide social media features and to analyze traffic to the site. We also share information about your use of our site with our trusted social media, advertising, email service providers, and analytics partners. [See details](https://www.bikebandit.com/help/security)

Unless you ask us not to, BikeBandit.com may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. To update your email preferences or to unsubscribe from our email mailing list, [click here](https://echo3.bluehornet.com/form/1046/801/preferences). 

You can also find out the following information at any time by contacting us:

  * See what data BikeBandit.com has about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data BikeBandit.com has about you.
  * Have us delete any data BikeBandit.com has about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

BikeBandit.com takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the BikeBandit.com website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever BikeBandit.com collects sensitive information (such as credit card data), it is encrypted and transmitted securely. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or by looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While BikeBandit.com uses encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only the employees who need your information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which BikeBandit.com stores personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you feel that BikeBandit.com is not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately.

Back to top

Contacting Customer Service

We do our best to answer all the frequently asked questions in the topics outlined above. If your question hasn't been completely addressed, use the links below to contact our Customer Service Staff.

Back to top

Customer Support Hours:  
Sales Department  
M - TH: 6:30am – 4:30pm Pacific   
Friday: 6:30am – 4:30pm Pacific

Customer Service Department  
M - TH: 6:30am – 4:30pm Pacific   
Friday: 6:30am – 4:30pm Pacific

Call Us!  
  
Toll Free! Pick Up the Phone  
and Dial **1-888-339-3888!**

Chat With Us!  
Log On to Our [Live Chat](http://server.iad.liveperson.net/hc/42100874/?cmd=file&file=visitorWantsToChat&site=42100874&referrer=http://www.bikebandit.com/help) to Speak  
with one of our Team Members!

Email Us!  
  
E-mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#82f1e7f0f4ebe1e7c2e0ebe9e7e0e3ece6ebf6ace1edef)  
Replies in about 1 business day, or less!
